<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 15:50:25 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openadx.eclipse.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First OpenADx project - Eclipse Cloe - in community review now</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/news/2019/06/17/first-openadx-project-eclipse-cloe-in-community-review-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/news/2019/06/17/first-openadx-project-eclipse-cloe-in-community-review-now/</guid>
      <description>The first open source project which will be contributed by the OpenADx Eclipse Working Group is now in the community review.
What is Eclipse Cloe? Eclipse Cloe is an enhanced middleware solution for closed-loop simulations, with a focus on functional software tests on system level. Cloe is used as a development tool for interactive and scripted workstation simulations, for code debugging, and for automated tests on servers. Cloe covers a central part of the verification and validation strategy, needed by all vendors in the field of Automated Driving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenADx Workshop - Forming an Eclipse Working Group</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-06-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-06-25/</guid>
      <description>Date: 25th June 2019
Location: Filderhalle Leinfelden-Echterdingen (near Stuttgart airport)
We are happy to invite you to our first meeting about forming the Eclipse OpenADx Working Group.
This event will bring all interested parties together for information about the Eclipse Working Group idea. Everyone is invited! We will also discuss technical aspects and continue our open exchange.
Please see the OpenADx Working Group wiki page for more information. The meeting is organized by the Eclipse Foundation and Bosch as an Eclipse member, and will be held under the Eclipse Bylaws (Eclipse Bylaws, Industry Working Group Process, Eclipse Intellectual Property Policy, Eclipse Anti-Trust Policy).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:09:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/projects/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse Cloe Eclipse Cloe provides simulation middleware and simulation-engine bindings for connecting simulation engines to the &#34;software under test&#34;.
Project Proposal
 Eclipse iceoryx Eclipse iceoryx is a middleware with a zero-copy shared memory approach which is optimized for the huge data inter-process-communication.
View Project
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:09:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/resources/</guid>
      <description>White Papers under construction
Articles Watch the video on OpenADx here on YouTube: https://youtu.be/7gHLkSzWNKA
 Blog Post: Autonomous Driving Toolchain Blog Post: Autonomous Driving Accelerator OpenADx launched Blog Post: 5 things you should know about OpenADx Blog Post: OpenADx reaches next level Vorteile von Open Source fuer ADAS und autonomes Fahren (only in German available)  Videos  YouTube: OpenADx - Leveraging open collaboration &amp;amp; OS to accelerate Autonomous Driving dev   YouTube: OpenADx &amp;ldquo;Autonomous Driving Simulation&amp;rdquo; Testbed – hardware in the loop (sponsored by Renesas)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technologies</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:09:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/technologies/</guid>
      <description>About Technologies Automated Driving (AD) is clustered into three equally important technology areas:
 In-vehicle technology Cloud technology (backend) Design, development, test and validation tools (tool chain)  OpenADx is currently focused on the AD tool chain. The goal is to accelerate AD development through open collaboration and open source.
OpenADx&amp;rsquo; vision is to ensure transparency and make the complex AD tool landscape more easily accessible for enterprise users.
Challenge AD is a complex challenge and therefore requires a multifaceted development process incorporating a variety of software tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:09:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/vision/</guid>
      <description>Autonomous driving (AD) is an extremely complex challenge with a complex development process, which is slowed at every turn by incompatibility between widely used development tools. The tools we already use in and of themselves are very good, but they do not work seamlessly with one another simply because they were never designed to work with each other. This is an industry-wide issue. It slows us all down in the race to automated driving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Group</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/working-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:09:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/working-group/</guid>
      <description>About The OpenADx working group will coordinate the development of Eclipse Foundation projects on the following topics:
 Implementation of interfaces between the development steps Implementation of common standards from other working groups (e.g. VDA Leitinitiative) Definition of an initial setup for fast implementation Ensures interoperability between development stages  Projects hosted by the Eclipse Foundation in the context of the OpenADx working group apply the Eclipse development process and best practices of openness, transparency and meritocracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AVL List GmbH</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/avl-list-gmbh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/avl-list-gmbh/</guid>
      <description>AVL - Development, testing &amp;amp; simulation of powertrain systems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eteration A.S.</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/eteration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/eteration/</guid>
      <description>ETERATION builds the right solutions for your organization, transforming it to a Digitally enabled body while leveraging your existing investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/ibm/</guid>
      <description>Rational software from IBM helps organizations create business value by improving their software development capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Itemis AG</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/itemis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/itemis/</guid>
      <description>itemis improves quality and cuts costs of software projects by the use of model driven software development (MDSD) and Eclipse based tool chains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JC Information Management GmbH</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/jc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/jc/</guid>
      <description>Our mission is to assemble scalable operations of platform-driven business models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Hat</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/redhat/</guid>
      <description>What began as a better way to build software&amp;ndash;openness, transparency, collaboration&amp;ndash;soon shifted the balance of power in an entire industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Bosch GmbH</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/bosch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/bosch/</guid>
      <description>The Bosch Group is a leading global supplier of technology and services in 4 business sectors: Mobility Solutions, Industrial Technology, Consumer Goods, and Energy and Building Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siemens AG</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/siemens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/members/siemens/</guid>
      <description>Siemens AG is a German engineering conglomerate, the largest of its kind in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>