<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on </title>
    <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/categories/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 16:21:43 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://openadx.eclipse.org/categories/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Embedded Software Engineering Kongress</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-12-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 16:21:43 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-12-02/</guid>
      <description>Date: 2nd - 6th December 2019
Location: Sindelfingen
ESE Kongress is Germany’s leading congress for the embedded software industry. Every December, more than 1,200 professionals get together to catch up on current technologies and methods, to discuss trends and to set the course for the future.
Learn more here&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AUTO.CODE Europe</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-11-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 16:18:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-11-28/</guid>
      <description>Date: 28th - 29th November 2019
Location: Berlin, Germany
auto:CODE 2019 is an international knowledge exchange platform, that will bring together for the first time the entire automotive value chain – From OEMs, Tier 1s through to software providers, to discuss and shape what DevOps really means for the industry and well as for your business. What impact will DevOps have, and how can you effectively implement DevOps to reap maximum benefits?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Conference - Software Drives - Transformation to Large Scale Distributed Automotive Software</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 16:05:15 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-11-12/</guid>
      <description>Date: 12th - 13th November 2019
Location: Mövenpick Hotel Stuttgart Airport
On 12 – 13 November 2019, decision-makers and developers from the industry will meet in Stuttgart to discuss the future of automotive software. At this year’s SOFTWARE DRIVES conference, we will focus on the transformation to large scale distributed automotive software:
 Data Software, architecture and system engineering Virtual simulation, verification and validation Open source: open software development, standardization and open interfaces  Find out more about OpenADx and &amp;ldquo;Open Source as a Way to Collaborate in a Changing Automotive Market&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THE IOT SOLUTIONS WORLD CONGRESS</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-10-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 16:00:05 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-10-28/</guid>
      <description>Date: 28th - 31st October 2019
Location: Barcelona, Spain
The IoT Solutions World Congress is the largest IoT event in the world to get inspired with new ideas, solutions and people. A unique event dedicated exclusively to joining IoT providers with industry in order to help the latter increase productivity via this disruptive technology. Since it’s first edition back in 2015, the event has grown to become the global reference for industrial IoT, and the annual meeting for industry stakeholders to establish new partnerships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon Europe - meet us there</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-10-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 15:54:12 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-10-21/</guid>
      <description>Date: 21st - 24th October 2019
Location: Ludwigsburg, Germany
EclipseCon Europe is the Eclipse Foundation’s primary event designed to create opportunities for the Eclipse community to learn, explore, share and collaborate on the latest ideas and information about Eclipse and its member companies. Every year EclipseCon Europe is rated as outstanding by attendees, speakers, and sponsors.
EclipseCon is all about community. Contributors, adopters, extenders, service providers, consumers, and business and research organizations gather to share their expertise and learn from each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenADx Workshop - Forming an Eclipse Working Group</title>
      <link>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-06-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openadx.eclipse.org/events/2019-06-25/</guid>
      <description>Date: 25th June 2019
Location: Filderhalle Leinfelden-Echterdingen (near Stuttgart airport)
We are happy to invite you to our first meeting about forming the Eclipse OpenADx Working Group.
This event will bring all interested parties together for information about the Eclipse Working Group idea. Everyone is invited! We will also discuss technical aspects and continue our open exchange.
Please see the OpenADx Working Group wiki page for more information. The meeting is organized by the Eclipse Foundation and Bosch as an Eclipse member, and will be held under the Eclipse Bylaws (Eclipse Bylaws, Industry Working Group Process, Eclipse Intellectual Property Policy, Eclipse Anti-Trust Policy).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>